So, the another method of persistence is wmi it is a Windows management instrumentation.
So, this is one of a best way to achieve persistence if you are if you are trying different
tactics. So, mostly in wmi there are three things ok. The important there is some important
things. So, the oneness even filter and the second one is even consumer and the third one
will be a even binding ok. So, let me show you let me teach you what what is that first
ok. So, here you can find a query. So, this this is the query you need to add the even
filter ok. So, if you want to create a persistence in wmi you have to do three things
you have to set a even filter and you have to set a even consumer then you have to bind
both of the even filters and consumer ok. So, this is the command to create a even filter
the command the filter name was a M E T R meter that was nothing but meter grader. And this
this even filter will be execute the 60 second ones after the windows get motor ok. So,
once the windows get logged on so, the our pair will be execute the 30 times sorry 60 second
ones ok. So, a pair will be get execute the 60 second ones ok. So, I already added I already
added the even filter all let me show you this is the command you can you can get information
about the even filter and a consumer. So, I have added previously each and everything
ok. So, I let me show you first. So, here you can find the even filter with the name
of M E T E R right. So, this is the name of a even filter which we have created with the
name of M E T E R. Let me show you the next thing the even consumer. So, the consumer is
like you needs to give the command what needs to get executed ok. So, in my point of
you I just created a persist mal.exe. One of the malware we have tried in registry persistence
the same malware we say have used here ok. So, that was sitting under the directory the
download folder. So, here you can find it was sitting here the persist mal.exe. So, I have
involved that in my even the consumer ok. So, the even filter is like the which time
which time the power payload needs to be executed ok. It will be like on log on log of
R it is like you are giving time frame like which time units to it needs to be get executed
away. So, you can change 60 seconds to 3600 or 5 minutes or something ok that is your
choice. This is called as the even filter. So, which time our payload needs to be get executed
at the time interval basically. The next one the even consumer this could be a command
line. So, what what needs to be get executed ok. The even the consumer what needs to
be get executed. Please take have executed this. Let me show you whether it was for this
is the command to verify ok. So, this is the command to verify whether everything everything
has been sited correctly. Let me execute this. So, now you can find there is one executable
get adder m e t e r and the executable path was a post system l dot e x e and the command
line was a post system l. So, you can find it was properly executed and it was successfully
added in the even consumer. The third thing was a binding. So, the binding is like
you are going to like combine both the things ok even filter plus even consumer equal to
binding ok. So, this is like to consumer binding. So, you are binding the even filter and
the even consumer ok. So, even filter name meter we have created even filter name ok meter
and even consumer name same of the meter. And this both the things are like binding ok.
So, let me execute this verification command. So, this is one of the you are you can refer
the WMA related active I will be giving this is in a resources and do not worry. So, let
me execute that. So, now, you can you can see there is a even filter and even consumer
or bind it properly. So, it was a it was a great thing. So, it has been binded and let
me start a reverse connection and let me restart the restarting mission and I will be
I will be start the reverse connection here. So, the port was 8 1969. So, here you can
find. So, the TCP handler has been started and let and wait for some some minutes let
our windows will be get restarter. The machine has been initiate let me give the password
and I will be good the machine will will see will be getting a reverse connection or not.
So, this is the one we have added in the starter folder you can see the path here name
equal to starter menu starter folder in the previous video I am not going to execute this
I will be going to cancel this ok. And let me wait for a few more minutes for a few more
seconds every 60 seconds after the computer get motor our payload will be get initiator
obviously added in WMI. So, now you can see I didn't initiate anything I didn't execute
anything. So, here you can see the reverse connection has been started let me execute the help
command and I will be executing 2MI here ok I need to execute few commands let me check
what commands we can we need to use file system commands networking command system command
ok execute a command let me give the option execute and I will try to execute a command execute
WMI flash all ok ok just creating a process but I don't need a process
I need the command to check a pretty village let me see which options you can use
system commands let me yeah here you can find a shell drop into a system commands let
me execute the shell ok I got shell now WMI flash all so here you can find it is a it
is an administrator and our privilege was system mandatory level because we have added that
you know of WMI Windows management instrumentation so we will be getting a system mandatory
level the higher place will be getting so I have that's all about the video I hope you
have a clear understanding about this let's pop off and we will connect to you in the next
video guys thank you bye